postadverts.com 2008-06-21

# 

Privacy Statement

Postadverts.com has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our customers. Postadverts.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to other companies. Your privacy is our upmost priority and we will do everything in our power to protect it.

**Personal Data Transmissions Are Encrypted**.  
When ordering from Postadverts.com, your personal details are encrypted. All information submitted through the signup forms are encrypted using Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the industry standard for encrypting personal information including credit card details.

**Does the Postadverts.com website use cookies?**  
If so, how are cookies used on the website? Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while visiting a site. Like most major websites, Postadverts.com uses cookies on certain pages of our site. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, we use cookies to inform us of a repeat visit and to help us improve our website and services.  
**  
How will I know about changes in the Privacy Policy?**  
Postadverts.com reserves the right to update this privacy policy from time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes.

If you have any questions about this document, Postadverts.com's information practices, or your dealings with Postadverts.com, please [Contact Us](mailto:info@postadverts.com).

This Privacy Policy was last updated April 2007.
